<resources>
    <string name="app_name">LittleKingsApp</string>

    <!--Name for Drinks-->
    <string name="MochaLatte">this is a simple recipe that you just need 3 ingredients to make – espresso (or coffee if you don’t have an espresso machine), milk, and chocolate syrup. </string>

    <string name="latte">A latte, or also called a caffè latte, is the big brother of the cappuccino, where everything revolves around the soft, silky foam. Usually the latte is made with a single or double shot of espresso
        (1/3 of your drink) and 2/3 of your drink is steamed milk with a small layer (around 1 cm) of frothed milk  </string>

    <string name="orangesmoothie">Starbucks Orange Mango Smoothie. A nourishing blend of natural orange mango juice,
    a whole banana, milk, whey protein, and fiber powder and ice.</string>

    <string name="orangevanilla">Vanilla Bean Crème Frappuccino® Blended Beverage. This rich and creamy blend of vanilla bean, milk and ice topped with
    whipped cream takes va-va-vanilla flavor to another level.</string>

    <string name="cappuccino">A cappuccino is the perfect balance of espresso, steamed milk and foam. This coffee is all about the structure and the even splitting of all elements into equal thirds. An expertly made cappuccino should be rich,
        but not acidic and have a mildly sweet flavouring from the milk. </string>

    <string name="ChaiLatte">A chai latte is made by mixing steamed milk with black tea that has been infused with spices. The drink is then topped with foam. The spices used will vary from café to café;
        some coffee shops create signature chai blends and keep the ingredients a secret.</string>

    <string name="tea">Right next to water, tea is hailed as the most consumed drink in the world. Every single drop of tea
    comes from the same type of plant</string>

    <string name="bubbletea">Bubble Tea is the name given to the wide variety of refreshing flavoured
    fruit teas and milk teas served ice cold or piping hot with chewy
    tapioca balls that you suck up through a big fat straw! .</string>

    <string name="Mochaccino">mochaccino is (us) the coffee drink cappuccino made with chocolate while coffee is a beverage made by infusing the beans of the coffee plant in hot water. of a pale brown colour, like that of milk coffee.
        (US) The coffee drink cappuccino made with chocolate.  </string>

    <string name="flatwhite">A flat white is a coffee drink consisting of espresso with microfoam (steamed milk with small, fine bubbles and a glossy or velvety consistency)</string>
</resources>